The store will not work correctly in the case when cookies are disabled.

**JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.** For the best experience on our site, be sure to turn on Javascript in your browser.

Toggle Nav [](https://www.nascoeducation.com/)[](https://www.nascoeducation.com/)[](https://www.nascoeducation.com/)

**Search**

Search

Search

* **Nasco Education Privacy Policy**

Privacy Policy
==============

[Click here for: California Consumer Privacy Policy | Do Not Sell My Information](https://www.nascoeducation.com/privacy-policy-ccpa)

This Privacy Policy explains how Nasco Education and its respective subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively “Nasco Education,” "Nasco," “we,” or “us”) collect and use information (as hereinafter defined) provided through our websites, however accessed (the “Site”). By using our Site and providing information to us, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect

The information we collect varies depending on the type of activity you are performing on our Site. Much of the Site can be accessed without providing any personal information. In all instances where we collect personal information through the Site, we specifically indicate what information is required in order to provide you with the product or service you have requested. We may gather the information which you directly provide including but not limited to: (i) name; (ii) email address; (iii) home or business address; (iv) username and password associated with your account; (v) phone number and other contact details; (vi) demographic information; (vii) credit or debit card information; (viii) product selections; and (ix) other details about you that you voluntarily provide (“Personal Information”).

### Other Information We Collect

At times we may also collect information which cannot be used to personally identify a user such as your server or connection’s unique identifier, the device, browser and version you are using, IP address, the web pages you visited prior to arriving on Site and once you leave, action on the Site, and searches (“Other Information”). We may also collect information through cookies or other similar tracking technology to provide you with a personalized buying experience, facilitate our marketing efforts, or analyze how we can best provide you targeted information or promotions.

### Cookies

We may use technologies such as cookies or other similar mechanisms. A cookie is a piece of data sent from a website that is stored by a user’s computer. The cookies allow us to among other things, remember your computer’s preferences, measure effectiveness of communications, web features and settings, generate usage reports and gather statistical data. Please be aware that many web browsers provide the capability to configure your cookie settings, however disabling cookies may limit the functionality of our Site. At times we may permit third-party companies to place advertisements on our Site. Such companies shall have the ability to place their own cookies, however they would not have access to the information we collect through Nasco Education cookies. Such other cookies would be subject to that company’s privacy policies. For more information on how we use Cookies and how to manage Cookies, see our [Cookie Policy.](https://www.nascoeducation.com/cookie-policy)

### How We Use Information

We use your information to provide you with the products and services requested, provide you with the best customer experience, create more personalized interactions with you, including providing you information about products and services that may interest you, and improve our products, services and Site. Examples of how we may use your information are below.

* Deliver our products and services as requested
* Communicate with you about our products or services
* Provide you with information about goods or services that may interest you
* Present more relevant display advertisements, and share promotional events
* Manage our product offerings, and assess the effectiveness of our marketing efforts
* Analyze and improve the functionality of our Site
* Improve our products, services, and business
* Prevent, detect, or investigate security concerns, including fraud
* Comply with applicable laws, regulations, or industry requirements
* Fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it or consent

### How We Share Information

We may share your information to deliver our products or services or to enhance your customer experience. More specifically, we share your information with third parties in the following circumstances:

* If you give us consent or permission to share the information.
* To those third parties who perform functions on our behalf, including support service providers, such as Site hosting, email and postal delivery, product and service delivery, analytics services, or other functions.
* In accordance with a business transaction. If we engage in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, other business transaction, we may share information subject to confidentiality arrangements.
* To prevent, detect, or investigate security concerns, including fraud.
* To protect and defend Nasco’s operations, rights, privacy, safety or property, or that of its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, employees, contractors, agents and/or partners.
* To comply with applicable laws, regulations, or industry requirements.
* With law enforcement if required by law or in order to prevent fraud or other potential wrongdoing.
* We do not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

### Access and Control of Your Information

We enable you to have control over the accuracy of your personal information. You can review and change the personal information you provide to us when setting up an account or processing a transaction by logging into the Site and visiting your account profile page.

You may use this [WEB FORM](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/8ed6873d-89f6-4178-aa13-e5d272719038/3b0bdde6-e73e-4bea-b6af-47b9f13a156c) to request access to, correct, or delete any other personal information that you have provided to us. In some cases, we cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to delete or change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement, cause the information to be incorrect, or for any other legally allowable reason.

### Your California Privacy Rights / Do Not Track

California residents visiting our Site may request that we not automatically gather and track information pertaining to their online browsing movements across the Internet. Such requests are typically made through web browser settings that control signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. We do not currently utilize the capability to respond to web browsers, and do not track signals or other mechanisms that provide you with the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of this information.

California Law also permits California residents to opt-out of our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes or to learn the categories of recipients and information disclosed. We do not, however, disclose your personal information to third parties in order for them to market their products and services to you.

### Security

We have implemented administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and/or alteration of your information. We utilize industry standard storage and protection procedures in order to safeguard Personal Information on servers which are not accessible to the public. No data storage or transmission plan is without risk. We cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

### Google Analytics

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site across devices. We have implemented the Remarketing and AdWords features of Google Analytics. The Remarketing feature allows us to serve you relevant advertising on third party websites if you have visited our Site, however accessed, but does not personally or directly identify you. AdWords allows us to manage our advertising and collect information about your visit to our Site. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings) You can opt-out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit the Site. For more information on opting-out of being tracked by Google Analytics, visit [Google Analytics Opt-out.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

### Leaving Our Site And/Or Linking to Third Parties

Because our Site is secure, your browser URL will inform you if you are leaving a secured portion of the Site. We strive to ensure that any information you send us is safe. When you leave this Site and go to another linked site, we are not responsible for the content or availability of the linked site. Please be advised that we do not represent either the third-party or you, if you enter into a transaction on the third party site. Further, the privacy and security policies of the linked site may differ from those practiced by us. We are not responsible for the practices of any partners or resellers including those who have a link on our Site.

### Changes

We reserve the right to change or revise this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes in the law or our data collection and use practices. New updates to the Privacy Policy will be posted to this Site so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Privacy policy changes will apply to the information collected from the date we post our revised privacy policy, as well as to existing information we hold. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. Your continued use of this Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes.

### FOR USERS IN THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA

If you are located in the European Economic Area (EEA), we provide you the following information and notification of rights in accordance with the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).

### Data Controller

Nasco Education obtains and processes personal information in different capacities. When you provide us with your information through our Site to purchase products, obtain information, subscribe to emails or newsletters, or otherwise communicate with us, we serve as a data controller. When we act as a data controller, we determine how Personal Data, as that term is defined by the GDPR, will be utilized in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data

Nasco Education’s legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it. Nasco Educationmay process your Personal Data because:

* We need to perform a contract or transaction with you
* You have given us permission to do so
* The processing is in our legitimate interests and is not overridden by your rights
* To comply with the law

### Your Data Protection Rights

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area, you have certain data protection rights. Nasco Education aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* **Request access to your Personal Data.** You may request access to any Personal Data we hold about you as well as related information, including the purposes for processing the Personal Data, the period for which the Personal Data will be stored, and the source of the Personal Data.
* **Request correction of your Personal Data.** You may have the right to obtain without undue delay the rectification of any inaccurate or incomplete Personal Data we hold about you.
* **Request erasure of your Personal Data.** You may have the right to request that Personal Data held about you is deleted. If you ever wish to correct or remove any personal information from our records, you may do so by contacting us at the email address below.
* **Object to processing of your Personal Data.** You may have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data where we are processing your personal data based on our legitimate interests and we cannot demonstrate compelling grounds to continue such processing or for our direct marketing.
* **Request restriction of processing your Personal Data Request.** You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information:

* During the pending period of time where we verify the accuracy of any personal data that you claim is inaccurate
* Where the processing of your personal data is unlawful but you oppose erasure and instead request that we restrict the use of your personal data
* If we no longer need your personal data but it is required for you to make or defend legal claims
* During the pending period of time where we verify our legitimate interest to process your data when you object to such processing

* **Right to Data Portability.** Where we process your personal data by automated means that you have provided to us based on consent or through contract, you have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine readable and commonly used format.
* **Withdraw your consent.** You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Nasco relied on your consent to process your personal information.

You also have the right to make a complaint to an EU Data Protection Authority if you believe that Nasco Education has not complied with its obligations under this Notice or European law.

### Retention of Data

Nasco Education will retain your personal data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your personal data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. Nasco Education will also retain data relating to the use of our Site (“Usage Data”) for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

**\*\*FOR USERS IN SWITZERLAND OR THE EUROPEAN UNION OR OTHER LOCATIONS OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES\*\* INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**

Nasco Education stores personal information in the United States. If you provide us information, it will be transferred to and accessed in the United States. This Privacy Policy shall apply even if we transfer personal information from non-United States countries to other countries.

YOU AGREE THAT THE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE AND SUBMIT VIA THE SITE IS BEING SENT TO THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA. YOU ARE INFORMED THAT THE UNITED STATES PRESENTLY DOES NOT HAVE AN ADEQUATE LEVEL OF PERSONAL DATA PROTECTION AS DETERMINED BY THE EUROPEAN COMMISSION’S ADEQUACY DECISION ON OCTOBER 6, 2015 (Case C-362/14) AND ARTICULATED IN THE EUROPEAN UNION’S GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION AND HAS NOT RECEIVED A SIMILAR DESIGNATION OF ADEQUACY BY ANY OTHER FOREIGN DATA PROTECTION AUTHORITY. YOU AGREE TO THE TRANSFER OF YOUR DATA AND PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE UNITED STATES, HOWEVER, TO BE USED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this policy, please contact us at: [websiteinquiry@nascoeducation.com.](mailto:websiteinquiry@nascoeducation.com)

Last Updated: February 8, 2024

Our contact info has changed! **[Click here](https://sftp-digital-assets.s3.amazonaws.com/Documents/Resources/ContactInfo2024.pdf)** to see the preferred way to reach us.

Free shipping for online orders over $199! Some [exclusions](https://www.nascoeducation.com/shipping-delivery) apply.

Free shipping for online orders over $199! Some [exclusions](https://www.nascoeducation.com/shipping-delivery) apply.

### Our company

### Customer support

### Resources and ideas

### Distributor / Dealer / Supplier

[](javascript:void(0);)

Customer Service 1.800.558.9595 • Copyright ©2023 Nasco
